[{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "6638e2c316c045c2e7069096"
  },
  "question": "Who is popularly known as Iron lady",
  "op1": "Mamtha Banarjee",
  "op2": "Indira Gandhi",
  "op3": "Selvi J.Jayalalitha",
  "op4": "Kalpana Chawla",
  "answer": "Selvi J.Jayalalitha"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "66390a1f16c045c2e70690a2"
  },
  "question": "Reactjs is a",
  "op1": "Library",
  "op2": "Framework",
  "op3": "Bank-end language",
  "op4": "Java package",
  "answer": "Library"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "663a3ab24eb132afb6074195"
  },
  "question": "When SSN college was started",
  "op1": "1995",
  "op2": "1996",
  "op3": "1997",
  "op4": "1998",
  "answer": "19996"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "663a550e16c045c2e70690c1"
  },
  "question": "Which language is considered as the mother of all languages",
  "op1": "English",
  "op2": "Tamil",
  "op3": "Hindi",
  "op4": "French",
  "answer": "Tamil"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "663a550e16c045c2e70690c2"
  },
  "question": "Brihadeeshwarar temple is located in",
  "op1": "Madurai",
  "op2": "Chennai",
  "op3": "Thanjore",
  "op4": "Thiruvannamalai",
  "answer": "Thanjore"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "663a550e16c045c2e70690c3"
  },
  "question": "Sri Sivasubramaniya Nadar college is currently located in which district",
  "op1": "Kancheepuram",
  "op2": "Chennai",
  "op3": "Chengalpattu",
  "op4": "Thiruvallur",
  "answer": "Chengalpattu"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "663a550e16c045c2e70690c4"
  },
  "question": "Who is considered as 'Kingmaker' in Indian politics",
  "op1": "Vijayakanth",
  "op2": "M.G.R",
  "op3": "Kamarajar",
  "op4": "Abdul kalam",
  "answer": "Kamarajar"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "663a550e16c045c2e70690c5"
  },
  "question": "Which programming language is not used in Web Development",
  "op1": "Python",
  "op2": "Java",
  "op3": "C",
  "op4": "JavaScript",
  "answer": "C"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "663a550e16c045c2e70690c6"
  },
  "question": "Pick Ramanujan's number",
  "op1": "7777",
  "op2": "1729",
  "op3": "1024",
  "op4": "1928",
  "answer": "1729"
},
{
  "_id": {
    "$oid": "663a550e16c045c2e70690c7"
  },
  "question": "What is the strength of CSE-A 3rd year class of SSN College",
  "op1": "68",
  "op2": "69",
  "op3": "70",
  "op4": "71",
  "answer": "69"
}]